一想起来就吓人
It scares us just thinking about it.
你们会觉得我们疯了的
When you hear it, you're gonna think we're insane.
说来听听，从头开始
Try us. Please, from the start.
一开始没什么，只是手脚在不同位置而已
It started out small,like a hand or a leg was in a different position.
然后它的脑袋变成了向上，而不是向下
Then its head was looking up instead of down.
然后有一天，它突然出现在另一个房间
And then one day, it was in a completely different room.
它会自己挪地方
It was moving around by itself.
是不是有人有你公寓的钥匙，跟你恶作剧？
Ever think maybe somebody had a key to your apartment and was playing a trick on you?
我们也这么想过
That's exactly what we thought.
但没有发现任何有人进来过的痕迹
But never once did we find any sign or evidence of intrusion.
(安娜贝尔事件 - 1968年)
所以你们认为这个娃娃是被附身了？
And this all led you to believe that the doll was possessed?
是的
Yes.
卡米拉联系过一位灵媒，她说有个名叫安娜贝尔·希金斯…
Camilla got in touch with a medium.We learned from her that a 7-year-old girl...
…的7岁小女孩曾经死在这个公寓里
...named Annabelle Higgins had died in this apartment.
她很孤独并且很喜欢我的娃娃
She was lonely and took a liking to my doll.
她只想要交朋友
All she wanted was to be friends.
我们知道这些后觉得她很可怜
When we heard this,we felt really sorry for her.
我们是护士，帮助人是我们的职责
I mean, we're nurses, we help people.
然后…
So...
…我们允许她进入了那个娃娃
...we gave her permission to move into the doll.
等等，你们做了什么？
Wait, you did what?
她想附身在娃娃里跟我们一起生活
She wanted to live with us by inhabiting the doll.
我们同意了
We said yes.
然后情况越来越糟
But then things got worse.
(想我吗？)
上帝啊
God.
我们回家的时候，她坐在走廊上
When we came home,she was sitting in the hallway.
但我们走的时候是把她放在空房间里的
But we had left her in the spare room.
黛比！黛比，等我！
Debbie! Debbie, wait!
我们吓坏了
We are beyond terrified.
不知道怎么回事、该怎么做，可以帮帮我们吗？
We don't know what's going on or what to do. Can you help us?
可以
Yes, we can.
首先，安娜贝尔并不存在，从来没有
Now, firstly, there's no such thing as Annabelle, and there never was.
鬼魂没有如此强大的力量
Ghosts don't possess such power.
我认为我们面对的是某种非常有心计
I think what we have here is something extremely manipulative.
某种凶残的东西
It's something inhuman.
你们对这娃娃的认识是非常错误的
It was a big mistake acknowledging this doll.
这样看来，是这个恶灵算计了你们
And through that,the inhuman spirit tricked you.
你们给了它侵扰你们生命的许可
You gave it permission to infest your lives.
什么是恶灵？
What's an inhuman spirit?
某种从未以人类形态出现过的
It's something that's never walked the earth in human form.
邪恶的东西
It's something demonic.
所以娃娃并没有被附身？
So the doll was never possessed?
不，不，这只是它的载体
No, no, it was used as a conduit.
它自己挪动位置，让人觉得是被附身了
It was moved around to give the impression of possession.
恶灵不会附身于物品，它们只会附身于人类
Demonic spirits don't possess things,they possess people.
它想占有你们的身体
It wanted to get inside of you.
很好，德鲁，可以关掉了
All right, that's good, Drew.You can shut it down now.
开灯
Hit the lights.
所以我们让教堂派了一位牧师过去
So we got the church to send a priest over...
给那房子以及住客进行了一次赐福
...to perform a blessing on the house and the occupants.
困扰那公寓的东西已经没有了，还有什么问题吗？
Whatever was oppressing that apartment was no longer with them. Any questions?
你
Yes.
那娃娃现在在哪？
Where's the doll now?
某个安全的地方
Someplace safe.
你  - 你们什么人？
Yep.  - So, what are you guys?
我是说，别人怎么称呼你们？
I mean, what do people call you?
嗯，好吧，有人称呼我们为“神鬼学家”
Uh, well, we've been called Demonologists.That's one name for us.
“猎魔人”，“灵异研究者”
Ghost hunters, paranormal researchers.
“怪人”
Kooks.
“疯子”
Wackos.
但我们更想被叫做“艾德和罗琳·沃伦”
But we prefer to be known simply as Ed and Lorraine Warren.
1960年起，艾德和罗琳·沃伦被认为是世上最著名的灵异现象调查者
罗琳拥有阴阳眼，艾德是天主教会唯一认可的神鬼学家
他们饱受争议的事业中经历了无数事件
唯有一件极度邪恶的事件，直到现在才为人所知
基于真实故事改编
《招魂》
1971年，哈瑞斯维尔，罗德岛
我们到了
Here we are.
哇噢，听到了吗？
Wow, hear that?
我什么都没听到  - 没错
I don't hear anything.  - Exactly.
好吧！
Oh. Okay!
好了，孩子们，我们到了！下车
Okay. Guys, we are here!Get out of the car.
上帝啊，我们在荒郊野外
Oh, God, we're in the middle of nowhere.
你们激动吗？给我个肯定的回答，是的！
Are you so excited?Where's my "yes"? Where's my "yes"? Yes!
比谁跑得快
I'll race you!
你们激动吗？  - 是的！
Are you guys excited?  - Yes!
我很激动！  - 快来，赛迪！
I'm so excited!  - Come on, Sadie!
我自己选房间！
I get my own room!
你开玩笑吧？不准挑房间！
Are you kidding me?No dibs on the rooms!
什么？  - 什么？
What?  - What?
那我可以自己选房间吗？还是也一样没得选？
So do I get to pick my own room?Or do I have no choice in that either?
她遇到心仪的男孩就会忘了新泽西的
Well, first cute boy she meets,she'll forget about Jersey.
很好  - 但愿
Great.  - I hope.
我等不及了
I can't wait.
过来，赛迪
Come on, Sadie.
赛迪，走吧
Sadie, let's go.
过来啊
Hey, come.
你怎么了？
What's the matter with you?
来啊，小妞
Hey, come on, girl.
好吧，随你
All right, suit yourself.
小心台阶
Watch your step.
借过
Coming through.
哇噢，小心，老爸
Whoa, watch out, Dad.
你想把它放在哪？  - 客厅
Where do you want it?  - In the living room.
安德莉亚，我的风铃在哪？  - 好像南希拿到另一个房间了
Andrea, where's my wind chime?  - I think Nancy's got it in the other room.
谢了！ 南希，看到我的风铃了吗？
Thanks! Hey, Nancy,have you seen my wind chime?
这个吗？  - 是的，谢谢
Oh, this one?  - Yeah, thanks.
自己来拿  - 南希！放手！给我
You're gonna have to catch it.  - Nancy! Let go! Give it here.
你太坏了
You're so mean.
妈妈，我可以挂风铃吗？
Hey, Mom, can I hang up my wind chime?
当然，外面有条绳子，你可以挂在那
Of course. There's a line outside you can hang it on.
亲爱的，把艾普丽尔叫进来好吗？天快黑了
Honey, have April come in, okay?It's gonna be dark soon.
好的
Okay.
过来，艾普丽尔！妈妈让我们进屋
Come on, April! Mom wants us inside!
看我找到了什么，辛蒂
Look what I found, Cindy.
一
One...
二
...two...
三
...three.
快，快，快，不准偷看
Come on, come on, come on.No peeking.
四
Four.
披萨吃完了吗？我不希望浪费
Are you guys done with the pizza?I don't want it going to waste.
快走  - 养你们这群小丫头很费钱啊
Let's go.  - It's expensive feeding you girls.
七，八，九
Seven, eight, nine, ten.
我该躲哪里？
Where should I hide?
准备好了吗，我来了！
Ready or not, here I come!
好，拍手
Okay, clap.
哇噢！  - 你们对这屋子还不熟悉
Whoa!  - Guys,You don't know the house well enough.
有人会受伤的
Someone's gonna get hurt.
我没事，我没事
I'm okay, I'm okay.
拍第二次
Second clap.
这是作弊
That's cheating.
拍手
Clap.
抓住你了！
Got you!
你没事吧？  - 还好
Are you okay?  - Um,Yeah.
弄坏了什么东西？
All right, what did we break now?
我不是故意的  - 麻烦请出来
I didn't mean to.  - Move out of there, please.
是克里斯蒂的错
It was Christine's fault.
老天  - 我的错？上帝啊
Oh, jeez.  - My fault? Oh, my God.
是克里斯蒂干的  - 不，我没有
Christine did it.  - No, I didn't.
你推我的  - 不，不，你自己退过去的
You pushed me.  - No, no, you fell back.
南希，帮我拿一下火柴，好吗？
Hey, Nancy, can you go get me the matches, please?
怎么了？
What's going on?
南希弄坏东西了  - 闭嘴
Nancy broke something.  - Shut up.
是你！
It was you!
什么坏了？  - 是墙
What broke?  - It's the wall.
哇噢！  - 我觉得好像是个地下室什么的
Whoa!  - I think we have a cellar or something.
我要看，我要看，让开，让开，让开
I wanna see, I wanna see. Move, move, move.
来，火柴，谢谢
Here, matches.Thank you.
我要看  - 你会看到的
I wanna see.  - You can see.
我要看嘛  - 你们都会看到的
I wanna see.  - You can all see.
走开！
Move!
天
Oh, man.
罗杰？
Roger?
下面有什么？
What do you see down there?
只是…呃，很难解释
Just, uh, hard to tell, you know?
一架旧钢琴，还有一堆垃圾
It's an old piano and a whole bunch of garbage.
啊，妈的…
Ah. Son of a...
哇噢
Wow.
罗杰？
Roger?
上来吧
Come on up.
我不希望你们下去那里
I don't want you girls going down there.
那里都是蜘蛛  - 呕！
That place is loaded with spiders.  - Ew!
别紧张
Just relax.
别这样，南希，这不好玩
Stop it, Nancy. It's not funny.
不管怎么说，我们有更多空间了，明早我再下去看看
We've got extra square footage anyway.I'll check it out in the morning.
我在想为什么要封起来  - 不知道
I wonder why it was boarded up.  - I don't know.
好了，孩子们，演出结束
Okay,guys.Show's over.
再五分钟  - 一分都不行
Five minutes.  - No more minutes.
赶紧上床，谢谢合作  - 上床
Up to bed. Please. Thank you.  - Right to bed.
累死了
Man, I'm fried.
赛迪有点不对劲
Something's up with Sadie.
是啊，不知道她怎么了，就是不肯进来
Yeah, I don't know what her problem is.Couldn't get her to come inside.
我们不能把她扔在那
We can't leave her out there.
没事的，我把她拴链子上了
She's all right. I got her on a chain.
赛迪，安静点
Sadie, hey, be quiet.
谢谢把这一切变为可能
Thanks for making this work.
我知道还有很多事要做
I know it was a lot to bite off.
会好起来，对吗？
It's gonna be great, isn't it?
我觉得已经很好了
I think it's great already.
是啊
Yeah.
你还累的无法打理新房子吗？
You still too fried to christen the new house?
谁说我累坏了？
Who said I'm fried?
谁都没有累坏
Ain't nobody here's fried.
妈妈？
Mom?
嗨，你们睡的还好吗？
Hey. How did you guys sleep?
我好冷
I'm cold.
的确有点凉
It is chilly, isn't it?
我们可以买一栋厕所实际可用的房子吗？
Do you think maybe we could have bought a house with a toilet that actually works?
跟你爸说去
Tell your father.
昨晚我房间里还有股怪味，好像什么东西死了一样
And there was a funky smell in my room last night. Like something died.
现在还有吗？  - 没了
Is it still there?  - No.
那就没问题了
Problem solved.
罗杰？
Roger?
在下面，亲爱的
Down here, honey.
早上好
Morning.
这可真得花一番大工夫了
This is gonna take some serious elbow grease.
是啊
Yeah.
上帝啊
Oh, my God.
这些东西该怎么处理？
What are we gonna do with all this stuff?
或许我们该先整理一下
Well, we probably ought to go through it
知道吗？可能有些很值钱的古董
You know?There might be some antiques down here worth a lot of  money.
或者只是一堆前任房主不要的废物
Yeah, or just a lot of junk the previous owner didn't want.
现在是我们的了  - 别做梦了
It's ours now.  - Knock yourself out.
我去煮点咖啡  - 好的
I'm gonna make some coffee.  - Okay.
我很快就上来，我要试试能否把这炉子修好
I'll be up in a minute,I'm gonna see if I can get this furnace working.
那就太好了，这里冷死了
Yeah, that'd be nice. It's freezing.
是啊
Yeah.
赛迪！来这里，赛迪！
Sadie! Come here, Sadie!
妈咪！
Mommy!
妈咪，赛迪在哪？
Mommy, where's Sadie?
她在外面，她现在一定很饿了，你去把她带过来吧
She's outside. You know, I'm sure she's hungry by now. Why don't you go and get her.
早上好，爸爸
Morning, Dad.
可以帮我拿一下吗？  - 当然
Can you hold this?  - Sure.
赛迪！  - 慢点，小皮猴
Sadie!  - Slow it down, Scoot.
罗杰  - 怎么
Roger.  - Yeah.
这钟停在了3:07，走廊那个也是
This clock stopped at 3:07,and so did the one in the hallway.
这倒挺奇怪的
That's weird.
可能是搬家的时候撞坏了吧
Maybe it got knocked around in the move.
说到撞坏，你昨晚对我做了什么？
Speaking of knocked around,what did you do to me last night?
这不是我干的，是我弄的吗？  - 我不知道
Ouch. I didn't do that. Did I?  - I don't know.
赛迪！
Sadie!
艾普丽尔！艾普丽尔！
April! April!
怎么…？艾普丽尔！发生什么事了？
What's...? April! What's going on?
怎么了？  - 上帝啊！
What happened?  - Oh, my God!
噢，赛迪
Oh, Sadie.
门罗，康乃狄克州，沃伦家
我们把所有东西都锁在这里了
We keep everything locked in here.
请随便参观
Feel free to look around.
就是别碰任何东西
Just don't touch anything.
哇噢
Wow.
太疯狂了
This is crazy.
这些都是从你们调查的案子中得来的吗？
So all these are taken from cases you've investigated?
是的，你所看到的一切，不是被诅咒的…
That's right. Everything you see in here is either haunted, cursed...
…就是曾被用于某种仪式的器物
...or has been used in some kind of ritualistic practice.
没有一样是玩具
Nothing's a toy.
甚至是那个玩具猴子
Not even the toy monkey.
别碰
Don't touch it.
好吧，是这些不可怕，还是你一点都不担心…
Oh,  Well, isn't it scary,or doesn't it worry you...
把这些东西放在家里？
...to have all these items right in your home?
所以我们才让牧师每个月来这房间赐福一次
That's why we have a priest that comes by once a month to bless the room.
我觉得…
Well, the way I see it is...
这些东西放这里比放在别的地方更安全
It's safer for these things to be in here than out there.
就跟不把枪带上街一个道理
It's kind of like keeping guns off the street.
为什么不把这些扔进焚化炉销毁掉？
Why not just throw them in an incinerator? Destroy them.
那样只是毁了它们的皮囊
Well, that would only destroy the vessel.
还是把妖怪封在瓶子里更好
Sometimes it's better to keep the genie in the bottle.
说起来，安娜贝尔娃娃在这里吗？
Say, is the, uh, Annabelle doll here?
这边走
Right this way.
好的
Yeah.
你说她只是个载体？  - 正确
You said she's a conduit?  - That's right.
那是什么意思？
What does that mean?
一个非常强大的恶魔把自己附着在她身上
A very powerful demonic has latched itself onto her.
那当你们在调查这些事件的时候…
So when you guys investigate these hauntings...
…是如何避免被他们缠上的呢？
...how do you stop them from latching onto you?
我们会做好一切预防措施
We have to take great precaution.
那你妻子呢？
But what about your wife?
她怎么了？
What about her?
哥顿神父告诉我…
Well, Father Gordon told me that...
那是不一样的
Well, that was different.
驱魔的时经常会有这样的事情发生
What happened to my wife happened during an exorcism.
有什么区别？
Well, what's the difference?
抱歉
Excuse me.
亲爱的，你在干吗？
Honey, what are you doing?
过来
Come here.
你更了解，是吗？
You know better. All right?
乔治安娜？
Georgiana?
你碰过什么东西吗？  - 没有
Come on. Did you touch anything?  - No.
好的，过来，亲爱的
All right, come on, honey.
乔治安娜！把朱蒂带上楼好吗？  - 噢，当然
Georgiana! Could you take Judy upstairs?  - Oh, sure.
无论如何你都不能进那间房间，还记得吗？
You can't go into this room,no matter what, remember?
是的，爸爸  - 好的
Yes, Daddy.  - All right.
去吧  - 好的，过来
Go on.  - Okay, come on.
我去给你找点零食，好吗？来吧
Let's see if I can find you a little snack, okay? Come on.
你们在做什么？
Hey. What's going on in here?
爸爸，看  - 你真漂亮
Daddy, look.  - You look very pretty.
好了，完成了，穿好衣服吃饭去
All right, all done.Go get dressed for dinner.
我就穿这个去吃饭  - 不，不行
I'm wearing it to dinner.  - No, you're not!
给你
Here you go.
怎么样了？
How'd it go?
我觉得他或许是想写一篇正面报道
Oh, I think he may write a positive article.
噢，一个有神论者
Ooh, a non-skeptic.
这是个不错的改变
That's a pleasant change.
是的
Yeah.
别再自责了
Stop blaming yourself.
没放糖
No sugar.
很快回来
Be right back.
这不好玩，南希
Not funny, Nancy.
什么？
What?
别抓我的脚
Stop grabbing my foot.
闭嘴，我什么都没做
Shut up, I didn't do anything.
是啊，是啊
Yeah, right.
别再放屁了
And stop farting.
真的很臭
It really stinks.
别怪我头上，是你自己
Don't blame that on me. It's you.
老爸？
Dad?
安德莉亚，为什么不睡觉？
Andrea, what are you doing out of bed?
那是什么声音？
What's that sound?
是辛蒂，她在我房间，她又梦游了
It's Cindy. She's in my room.She's sleepwalking again.
我从没见过她这样子
I've never seen her do this before.
我记得你说梦游的时候不要吵醒她
I remembered you saying not to wake her if she's like this.
是的，我们把她放回床里
No, we just put her back to bed.
嗨，嗨，宝贝，嘘
Hey, hey. Sweetie. Shh.
我们回床里去
Let's go back to bed.
她没事了，晚安
She's okay. Good night.
晚安
Night.
她又梦游了？好久都没这样过了
She's sleepwalking again?She hasn't done that for awhile.
她停在了安德莉亚的房间里，吓坏她了
She ended up in Andrea's room too.I think kind of freaked her out.
这不太妙，我们该怎么做？  - 不知道
That's not good. What are we gonna do?  - I don't know.
亲爱的，这里又有一块淤青了  - 嗯？
Honey, you got another bruise here.  - Hmm?
疼吗？
Does that hurt?
真奇怪
That's weird.
我不知道，要不要去看一下医生？
I don't know. Will you do me a favor,go see a doctor for that?
好，我会的，开车小心  - 知道了
Yeah, I will. Drive safe.  - Yeah.
我爱你  - 我也爱你
I love you.  - I love you too.
再见！
Bye!
爱你们！
Love you!
辛蒂，拿午餐了吗？  - 拿了
Cindy, you have your lunch?  - Yeah.
是的
Yes, I do.
我很想赛迪
I miss Sadie a lot.
她是我最好的朋友
She was my best friend.
你是我的朋友，对吗？
You're my friend, right?
好的，我们一起玩吧
Yeah, let's play.
你在跟谁说话？  - 罗利
Who are you talking to?  - Rory.
罗利？
Rory?
他是我的新朋友  - 噢，是吗？
He's my new friend.  - Oh, really?
是的，你想见他吗？  - 好啊，怎么见？
Yeah, do you want to see him?  - Yeah. Uh-huh. How?
用这个
With this.
当音乐停的时候，你会看到他在镜子里，站在你身后
When the music stops, you see him in the mirror standing behind you.
好吧
Okay.
但你得拧发条
But you have to twist the key.
好的
Okay.
砰！妈咪！  - 噢！
Boo, Mommy!  - Oh!
艾普丽尔，你吓死我了  - 中招！
April, you just gave me a heart attack.  - Got you!
好吧，我猜罗利不想见我，是吗？
Well, okay, I guess Rory doesn't want to see me, huh?
噢，好吧
Oh, well.
我们可以玩捉迷藏吗？
Can we play hide-and-clap?
捉迷…？噢，亲爱的，我不想玩
Hide-and-cla--?Oh, honey, I don't want to play.
求你！她们都不让我玩  - 好吧，好吧
Please! Nobody ever lets me play.  - Okay, okay.
记住，你得要求我拍三次手
Remember, you get to ask me for three claps.
好的
Okay.
一，二，三
One, two, three.
我要躲起来了！  - 好的
I'm gonna go hide now!  - Okay.
四，五…
Four, five...
六，七…
...six, seven...
八，九…
...eight, nine...
十！
...ten!
拍第一次手！
First clap!
噢，该死
Ow. Shit.
拍第二次手！
Second clap!
艾普丽尔
April.
我知道你藏在哪里
Oh, I know where you're hiding.
拍第三次手
Give me the third clap.
我要把你抓出来喽
I'm gonna get you now.
我听到你呼吸了
I can hear you breathing.
艾普丽尔
April.
你把眼罩拿下来了，我赢了！
You took your blindfold off. I win!
你一点都不用心，妈妈，我在克里斯蒂跟南希的房间
You weren't even warm, Mom.I was in Christine and Nancy's room.
总得给我留一条路线，不然我会失去卡车保险的
I gotta have some routes here,or I'm gonna lose the insurance on the rig.
这才只有半价啊，兄弟
That's like half of my rate, man.
嗯，好的
Yeah, okay.
我…好吧，我接下了
I'll, uh... Yeah, I'll take it.
谢谢
Thank you.
什么路线？  - 是…佛罗里达
What's the route?  - It's, uh, Florida.
往返一个星期，我明天出发
It's a week turnaround. I start tomorrow.
我们会撑过去的
We'll get through this.
是的
Yeah.
来，去睡觉吧
Come on, let's go to bed.
住手，南希，这一点都不好玩
Stop it, Nancy. It's not funny anymore.
我要睡觉，求你别再抓我的脚了
I'm trying to sleep,please stop grabbing my feet.
南希？
Nancy?
你在干吗？
What are you doing?
克里斯蒂？
Christine?
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
你看到了吗？
Do you see it?
看到什么？
See what?
有人在门后
There's someone behind the door.
什么？
What?
有个人站在那里
There's someone standing over there.
我没看到任何人
I don't see anyone.
它正看着我们
It's looking right at us.
南希，不要！南希
Nancy, don't! Nancy.
不，不，你看，你看
No, no. Look. Look.
看，没有人，看到了吗？
Look, there's no one...no one here. See?
又是那味道
Ugh. It's that smell again.
噢，上帝啊
Oh, my God.
它就站在你背后
It's standing right behind you.
克里斯蒂？！克里斯蒂！克里斯蒂！
Christine?! Christine! Christine!
天，开不了…
God, it won't op...
克里斯蒂！  - 不！不！不！
Christine!  - No! No! No!
怎么了？发生什么事了？  - 有个人在这里！
What's going on? What happened?  - There was someone else in here!
什么？  - 哪里？
What?  - Where?
门边，它在门背后
By the door. It was behind the door.
宝贝，什么都没有，没人在那里
Honey, there's nothing in here.There's nobody in here.
有个人在这里！
There was someone else in here!
我正在睡觉，然后觉得有人抓着我的脚
I was just sleeping, and then I felt somebody grab my feet.
我以为是南希
So I thought it was Nancy.
宝贝，我非常确定那只是个噩梦
Well, honey, I'm pretty sure that it was just a bad dream.
不是！它跟我说话了！
No! It talked to me!
它说…
It said...
它想要我们全家都死掉
...that it wants my family dead.
温斯顿先生！
Mr. Winston!
温斯顿？温斯顿？
Winston? Winston?
到他后面
Get behind him.
你要去哪？
Where you off to?
打算去店里买点东西
I just gotta run to the store for a few things.
为什么要这样？  - 什么？什么意思？
Why do you even try?  - What? What do you mean?
15年来，你有哪次是能骗过我的？
In 15 years have you ever been able to lie to me?
哥顿神父打电话来，说他有个案子想让我们跟进一下
Father Gordon called. He's got a case he wants us to look into.
我说我会过去看看的，罗琳，是“我”会
I said I'd go check it out myself.Lorraine, myself.
我跟你一起去
I'm going with you.
我知道你担心那个会再次发生
I know you're worried it's gonna happen again.
是啊，千真万确
Yeah, I am. I really am.
或许我们该歇一歇了，写本书什么的
Maybe it's just time we take a break.Write that book.
还记得结婚那晚你跟我说了什么吗？
Do you remember what you said to me on our wedding night?
“能再来一次吗？”
"Can we do it again?"
在这之后
After that.
你说上帝把我们撮合在一起是有原因的，对吗？
You said that God brought us together for a reason. Right?
我很确定不是为了写书什么的
I'm pretty sure it's not to write a book.
我去穿件衣服
I'm gonna get dressed.
我们已经确定那东西就在这阁楼上
We've isolated the disturbances to the attic.
你们听
Now I just want you to listen for a second.
噢，上帝啊，就是这个
Oh, my God, that's it.
再来一次，艾德
Do it again, Ed.
现在只是我在踩地板而已，但你们从水管里放水的时候
Right now it's just my weight.But you take the water coming off the pipe...
会把风从那破窗子里带进来
...combined with the wind coming through the broken window...
然后这些木条就会胀大，互相摩擦
...these boards are gonna expand and rub against each other.
满屋子都有这声音，是因为这些管子是连着暖气片的
You heard it all through the house because of these pipes leading to the radiator.
所以这地方并没有闹鬼？
So this place isn't haunted?
是的，不太可能
No, it rarely is.
有时候的确是可以有合理解释的
Yeah, there's usually always some kind of rational explanation.
丫头们，该睡觉了
Girls, it's way past your bedtime.
是谁？
Who is that?
谁在下面，我要把你关起来了
Who's ever down there,I'm gonna lock you in now!
救命！
Help!
安德莉亚，救命！
Andrea! Help!
嗨，想玩捉迷藏吗？
Hey, wanna play hide-and-clap?
辛蒂？
Cindy?
好吧，那…
Okay, now....
是这样吗？
All right?
没错，过来
All right, come on.
过来
Come on.
就这样
There you go.
好了，今晚就跟我一起睡了，好吗？
Okay, you can just sleep with me tonight,all right?
来
There you go.
对了
There.
安德莉亚？  - 救命！救命！救命！
Andrea?  - Help! Help! Help!
谁在里面？  - 安德莉亚？
Who's in here?  - Andrea!
安德莉亚？安德莉亚！
Andrea? Andrea!
在这里！
In here!
救命，爸爸！救命，是安德莉亚！
Help, Daddy! Help, it's Andrea!
谁在这里？  - 安德莉亚！
Who's in here?  - Andrea!
发生什么事了？
What happened?
该死的，谁能告诉我这里发生了什么事？
Somebody, goddamn it,tell me what's going on here?
恐惧就是，未知事物或强烈危机感所致的…
Fear is defined as a feeling of agitation and anxiety caused by the presence...
情绪波动及焦虑
...or imminence of danger.
无论是鬼魂、妖魔还是邪物，都以此为生
Whether it's a ghost, a spirit or an entity, they all feed on it.
(马萨诸塞西部大学，韦克菲尔德)
这是莫里斯
Take Maurice here.
一个三年级都没念完的加籍法裔农民
A French-Canadian farmer with no more than a third-grade education...
被附身之后，说着一口我听过最标准的拉丁语
...yet after he was possessed,spoke some of the best Latin I'd ever heard.
有时还倒过来说
Sometimes backwards.
他一直被他的父亲骚扰、折磨着
He'd been molested by his father,who had also tortured him repeatedly.
一个把他当做宿主的暗灵
A dark spirit made its home in this man.
你们看他的眼睛，会发现他在流血泪
Now, if you look into his eyes,you can see him tearing blood.
还有这样…
And like that...
…从身体里浮现出一个倒十字架
...an upside-down cross started to appear from within his body.
好，德鲁，可以开灯了
All right, Drew, you can hit the lights.
你会亲自主持驱魔仪式吗？
Did you personally perform the exorcism?
不，我没有被授权，但我协助过很多
No, I'm not authorized.But I've assisted on many.
要知道，驱魔是非常危险的…
See, an exorcism can be very dangerous...
不仅只对受害者而言，对屋里的所有人都一样
...not only for the victim,but for anyone in the room.
莫里斯怎样了？  - 他试图杀了他妻子…
What happened to Maurice?  - He tried to kill his wife...
…但只打伤了她的胳膊，然后他把枪对准了自己
...but instead shot her in the arm and then turned the gun on himself.
莫里斯的生活很悲惨…
Maurice had a very troubled life with little to live for...
…甚至连驱魔都无法救回他
...and not even an exorcist could bring him back.
由此，让我们看一下恶魔活动的三个阶段
Which brings us to the three stages of demonic activity:
出现，骚扰，附身
Infestation, oppression and possession.
首先，“出现”
Now, infestation:
一般就是说话声、脚步声以及感觉有另外一个人存在…
That's the whispering, the footsteps,the feeling of another presence...
…很快就会发展成第二阶段“骚扰”，
...which ultimately grows into oppression, the second stage.
所以受害者一般都是那些…
Now this is where the victim,and it's usually the one...
…比较容易受外部力量影响的…
...who's the most psychologically vulnerable...
…心理承受能力比较差的人
...is targeted specifically by an external force.
把受害者吓倒，摧毁他们的意志
Breaks the victim down.Crushes their will.
在他们最脆弱的时候，就发展到了最后也就是第三阶段，“附身”
And, once in a weakened state, leads them to the third and final stage: possession.
嗨，艾德？罗琳？  - 是的
Hey, Ed? Lorraine?  - Yeah.
有人想跟你们聊聊
There's someone here that would like to talk to you.
嗨  - 谢谢，德鲁
Hi.  - Thanks, Drew.
谢谢  - 没事，待会儿见
Thank you.  - Sure，I'll see you later.
有什么可以帮你的？
How can we help you?
我房子里发生了很可怕的事情，你们可以来看一下吗？
There's something horrible happening in my house. Could you come and take a look?
嗯…呃…今天有点晚了
You know, uh, it's getting kinda late.
我们要回家了  - 不，你们不明白
We really need to be head to our family.  - No,You don't understand.
事实上我们知道，很多东西是可以有合理解释的…
But we do. There's usually some sort of rational explanation...
我五个女儿都被吓坏了，我担心这东西会伤害我们
I have five daughters who are scared to death.I'm so afraid this thing wants to hurt us.
你们也有女儿，难道你们就不会竭尽所能去保护她吗？求你们
You have a daughter. Wouldn't you do anything you could to protect her? Please.
求你们来看一下可以吗？
Please can you come and take a look?
好的，当然
Of course we will.
孩子们，赶紧整理一下，谢谢
Hey,You guys straighten up? Thanks.
你好  - 嗨
Hello. Hi.  - Hi. Hi.
非常感谢能来
Thanks for coming.
你好，我是罗杰  - 罗琳
Hi, I'm Roger.  - Lorraine.
你好，幸会，罗杰，我是艾德·沃伦
Hey, nice to meet you, Roger. Ed Warren.
非常感谢能来  - 请进来吧
Thanks for coming.  - Please, come in.
谢谢
Thank you.
那…
So....
噢，天啊，看看，这些美女们都是谁？
Oh, my God. Look at you all.Who are these beautiful young women?
这是安德莉亚，老大，南希、辛蒂、克里斯蒂…
This is Andrea, the oldest,Nancy, Cindy, Christine...
…还有艾普丽尔
...and April.
这是沃伦先生和沃伦太太
It's Mr. and Mrs. Warren.
我们现在都睡在楼下
We're all sleeping down here now.
孩子们有点安全感，也更暖和一些
The girls feel safer and it's warmer.
我一直开着暖气，但这房子就是冷得要命
I'm constantly turning up the heat,but the house is always freezing.
炉子没什么问题
It's not a problem with the furnace.
我是说，我找不出原因
I mean, not that I can find.
前几晚情况越来越糟糕了
It's gotten a lot worse the past few nights.
有股难闻的味道，像烂肉一样，满屋子都是
There's this awful smell, like rotting meat.It moves around the house.
呃…
Uh....
什么？怎么了？
What? What is it?
腐臭味有可能是某种恶魔活动征兆
Well, rancid smells could indicate some type of demonic activity.
噢，上帝啊
Oh, my God.
这是为了防止晚上发出碰门声
That's to keep those doors from banging at night.
不然，整晚都会像这样响个不停
Otherwise, it's like...All night long, just like that.
每天都会发生？  - 是的
Does it come in threes?  - Yeah.
天亮就停？
It stops at dawn?
对
Uh-huh.
有时这意味着对三圣的不敬
Well, sometimes it's meant as an insult to the Trinity:
圣父、圣子、圣灵
The Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit.
知道吗，这是非常邪恶的东西，但我们有办法…
You know, it's the damndest thing,but we also get all kinds of birds...
…可以把它从这房子里找出来消灭掉
...that will just fly against the side of the house and break their necks.
是吗？
Hm. Really?
钟都停在了凌晨3:07
And the clocks stop at 3:07 a.m.
所有的？  - 每个都是
All of them?  - Every one.
噢，这些原本都是挂在楼梯上的
Oh, we were hanging those along the stairs.
有东西老是会把它们弄下来，所以就不挂回去了
Something just kept knocking them down,so we stopped hanging them up.
我一直在说
That's what I was talking about.
我们搬来的时候它就已经在了
It was here when we moved in.
地下室里还有很多东西
There's also a lot of stuff in the cellar.
带我去地下室看看
Show me the cellar.
看看她都让我干了些什么
Look what she made me do.
发现什么了吗，亲爱的？
You picking up anything in here, hon?
这里发生过很可怕的事情，艾德
Something awful happened here, Ed.
这些淤青，是来这里之后出现的吗？
Those bruises, they from something that happened here?
这是因为我身体缺铁什么的
Oh, it's some iron deficiency thing I have.
发生了那么多事，你们为什么不搬走？
You know, with all that's been going on,why haven't you just moved out?
不知道我们可以搬去哪
I don't know where we'd move to, you know?
我们把所有钱都花在了这里，还进行了很多整修
We got all our money tied up in this place and had a lot of repairs on top of that.
我也不知道谁可以长期收留我们一家七口人
And I don't know anybody whose gonna take in a family of seven indefinitely.
所以我们找到了你们
That's why we tracked you down.
很荣幸你们能来找我们
We're glad you found us.
好，开始吧
All right, let's get started.
我叫艾德·沃伦，今天是1971年11月1日
My name is Ed Warren.It's November 1st, 1971.
我现在跟卡洛琳·佩伦坐在一起…
I'm sitting here with Carolyn Perron...
…她的家庭正经历着灵异事件
...who, with her family, has been experiencing supernatural occurrences.
好，开始吧
Okay, go ahead.
从哪里说起？
Where do I start?
从初次异常现象开始
From the first occurrence.
我觉得应该是那些钟
I guess it was the clocks.
爸爸妈妈跟我说你有个朋友
Mom and Dad tell me that you have a friend.
他叫罗利，他也住在这里
His name's Rory.He lives here too.
嗯  - 但他一直很悲伤
Hmm.  - But he's always sad.
为什么？
Why is that?
他不告诉我，可能有什么不好的事情发生在他身上了
He won't tell me but I think something bad happened to him.
可以让我见见罗利吗？
Do you mind if I try to see Rory?
嗨
Hey.
怎么了？
What is it?
我们是从银行拍卖来的，所以不知道之前谁住在这里
We bought it at auction from the bank, so,you know, we never knew who lived here.
罗琳跟我都觉得你们的房子需要“清洁”一下
Well, Lorraine and I both feel that what your house needs is a cleansing.
一场驱魔仪式
An exorcism.
什么，驱魔？
What, exorcism?
我一直以为驱魔是仅针对人的
I thought that was something that you do to people.
不，不一定的
No, not necessarily, no.
我们得离开这里
We have to get out of here.
恐怕这于事无补
I'm afraid that's not gonna help.
罗琳看到了一些…
Lorraine saw something, which--
你说吧，亲爱的
Go ahead, hon.
我看到你们的房子里有邪恶之物出没
I've been seeing the dark entity that haunts your house...
…外面也有
...and your land.
第一次看到它是在走进你们家门的时候
I saw it first when I came through your door.
它就靠在你背上
It was latched to your back.
第二次是在走进客厅的时候，它跟女孩们在一起
And then I saw it again with the girls when we walked into the living room.
无论你们去哪里…
And it doesn't matter where you go...
…这邪物会一直跟着你们
...this dark entity has latched itself to your family...
…吸食你们
...and it's feeding off you.
哪怕我们离开也一样？
Even if we leave?
有时候鬼缠身，就像是踩到了口香糖
Sometimes when you get haunted,it's like stepping on gum.
会一直粘着你
You take it with you.
我得说，你们这里有很多幽灵…
Look, I gotta tell you,you have a lot of spirits in here...
…但这个是我们最担心的，因为它充满了仇恨
...but this is the one that I'm most worried about, because it is so hateful.
好吧，那我们该怎么做？叫个牧师来吗？
Okay, so what do we do?Can we call a priest?
那么简单就好了
I wish it were that easy.
驱魔是一种很古老的仪式，需要很多年的训练
Performing an exorcism is an archaic procedure. Requires years of training.
哪怕这样，惨剧还是会时常发生
And even then,I have seen it go horribly wrong.
但在这之前，首先要获得教堂的授权
But before we even get that far,the church has to authorize it first.
就是说我们要调查、收集证物及提供证据…
It means we gotta investigate,gather evidence and provide proof...
…这才是难点
...and that's the hard part.
孩子们受过洗礼吗？
Have your children been baptized?
不，没有，我们不常去教堂
Uh, no, we never got around to that.We're not really a churchgoing family.
或许应该重新考虑一下，我们的出现或许会让事情更糟糕
Well, you may want to rethink that.Our presence here could make things worse.
为什么？
Why?
因为我们是个威胁
Because we're a threat.
这里这家伙不太会喜欢我们
And whatever you're dealing with here isn't gonna like us.
目前为止它还没施过暴，这是个好现象
So far it hasn't done anything violent,and that's a good sign.
所以我们会让我们的人调查一下这里…
So we're gonna have our guy do some homework on the property...
…看看我们要对付的是什么东西
...to see what we're up against.
朱蒂，你要干吗？
Judy, what are you up to?
我有礼物给你
I got you a present.
我跟外婆在教堂的庭院市场上买的
Me and Nanna got these at the church's yard sale.
宝贝  - 一个给你，一个给我
Honey.  - One for you and one for me.
她在我这个里…
She put a picture...
…放了你和爸爸的照片
...of you and Daddy in mine.
外婆说这样我们就会永远在一起
Nanna said this way we'll always be together.
你我会一直在一起的
You'll be with me and I'll be with you.
我想你和爸爸
I miss you and Daddy.
嗨，亲爱的
Hey, hon.
在
Yup.
你不会相信的，卡洛琳的声音没录下来
You're not gonna believe this.Carolyn's voice didn't record.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
听着
Listen.
我叫艾德·沃伦，今天是1971年11月1日
My name is Ed Warren.It's November 1st, 1971.
现在跟卡洛琳·佩伦坐在一起…
I'm sitting here with Carolyn Perron...
…她的家庭正经历着灵异事件
...who, with her family, has been experiencing supernatural occurrences.
好，开始吧
Okay, go ahead.
从初次异常现象开始
From the first occurrence.
什么都没有
Nothing.
全程都是
The whole time.
不知怎么回事，发现什么了吗？  - 很多
I don't know. You find anything?  - Lots.
我是说，怪不得他们会经历这些
I mean, it's no wonder they're going through what they are.
这是之前的农场房子
That's the original farmhouse.
是1863年一个名叫杰德森·佘曼的人建造的
It was built in 1863 by a man named Jedson Sherman...
…他娶了一个名叫巴斯希巴的女人
...who was married to a woman named Bathsheba.
艾德，她是玛丽·汤·艾斯黛的亲戚
Ed, she's related to Mary Towne Estye.
是被指控在赛伦实施巫术行为的女巫之一
She was one of the women accused of witchcraft in Salem.
被判了绞刑  - 哇噢
She was hung during the trials.  - Wow.
巴斯希巴嫁给杰德森之后，生了个孩子…
After Bathsheba married Jedson,they had a baby...
…当孩子7岁的时候…
...and when the baby was 7 days old...
…杰德森发现她在壁炉边献祭
...Jedson caught her sacrificing it in front of the fireplace.
她跑到了码头那的树边…
She ran out to that tree by the dock...
…爬了上去，表达了对撒旦的崇拜
...climbed up, proclaimed her love to Satan...
…诅咒了每一个试图夺走她土地的人，然后上吊自杀了
...cursed anyone who tried to take her land, and hung herself.
宣称的死亡时间是凌晨3:07
Time of death was pronounced at 3:07 in the morning.
那一些事情就有解释了
Well, that explains a few things.
对，还有这个
Yeah, so does this.
她姓沃克，30年代的时候住在那里
Her last name's Walker.She lived there in the '30s.
她有个叫罗利的孩子在树林里神秘失踪了
She had a boy named Rory who ysteriously disappeared in the woods.
然后她在地下室自杀了
Then she killed herself in the cellar.
这还不算完
And that's not all.
自从原本200英亩的农场被分块卖掉之后
So, what was the original 200-acre farm as since been subdivided and sold off.
有个男孩在这个池塘里淹死了，他住在这里
There was another boy who drowned in pond here. He lived in a house over here.
还有一个在附近做佣人的女人，也自杀了
And a woman who worked as a maid in a eighboring home, she committed suicide too.
夺走她土地的人
People who took her land.
现在跟卡洛琳·佩伦坐在一起…
I'm sitting here with Carolyn Perron...
…她的家庭正经历着灵异事件
...who, with her family, has been xperiencing supernatural occurrences.
好，开始吧
Okay, go ahead.
从初次异常现象开始
From the first occurrence.
布拉德来了
Here's Brad.
路好找吗？  - 是的
You find it okay?   - Oh, yeah.
德鲁，这是布拉德警官
Drew, this is Officer Brad.
布拉德·汉密尔顿警官，罗德岛哈瑞斯维尔警局的
Officer Brad Hamilton,Harrisville, Rhode Island P.D.
很高兴见到你
Hm. Nice to meet you, man.
你是那个幸运的新警察，是吗？  - 应该是吧
So you're the lucky new cop, huh?  - Guess so.
鬼魂用枪是打不死的，知道吗？  - 对他友好一点，德鲁
You know you can't shoot ghosts, right?  - Take it easy on him, Drew.
好了，兄弟们，帮我把这些东西搬下车
All right, guys,help me get this stuff unloaded.
你拿这个
You take this.
嗨，罗杰
Hi, Roger.
这边好了之后，再上楼去看看，好吗，德鲁？
All right. When you're finished here,why don't you hit upstairs, all right, Drew?
知道了
You got it.
这车哪里坏了？
What's wrong with the Chevy?
她还有哪里是完好的吗？
Ugh, what's not wrong with her?
需要换个新化油器才能启动  - 是吗？
Needs a new carburetor to start.  - Oh, yeah?
看来维修得停工一阵子了
Kind of put fixing her up on hold for a while.
嗯，是啊
Yeah. Ahem.
布拉德，把温控器拿给我，好吗？
Hey, Brad, hand me a thermostat,would you?
这是干什么用的？
What's this, uh, do?
当气温瞬间下降的时候…
When there's an instant drop in temperature...
…温控器就会激发相机拍一张照片
...the thermostat triggers the camera to take a picture.
你用这玩意儿拍到过东西吗？
You've actually caught things on film?
是的，这才是重点
Well, yeah, that's, uh, the point.
为什么…为什么在这里？
Why,uh...? Why out here?
这是那女巫自杀的地方
Well, this is where the witch committed suicide.
她在你头顶的那根树枝上吊死了
She hung herself from that branch right above where you're standing.
为什么母亲会杀了她亲生孩子？
How could a mother kill her own child?
对她来说这并不是孩子
It was never a child to her.
她只是把她当作工具来攻击上帝
She just used her God-given gift as the ultimate offense against him.
女巫们相信撒旦可以提升她们的能力
Witches believe it elevates their status in the eyes of Satan.
那天在海滩玩得很开心，是吧？
Wow.That's a nice day at the beach, huh?
你怎么知道的？
How did you know?
这是一种能力，就像是透过窗帘窥视别人的生活一样
It's an insight. It's like a peek through the curtain into another person's life.
那一天对我意义非凡，我们正沿着海岸开车
That day meant so much to me.We were driving along the coast.
南希说那里很漂亮
Nancy pointed out how pretty the view was.
我想这是个拍照的好时机
I thought this is a perfect opportunity for a photo.
我们正打算重新开始，新的房子，新的起点
We're gonna start fresh, you know?A new house, a new beginning.
你也见过罗杰跟姑娘们了，我从没见他们那么开心过
You should have seen Roger and the girls.I've never seen them so happy.
茄子！
Cheese!
他们对我来说就是一切
They mean the world to me.
把你的手平放在桌子上
Put your hand flat on the desk.
好，然后拿开
Yeah, and take it off.
开始了
Here we go.
看到了吗？
See?
这能让我们看到那些肉眼看不到的东西
It just reveals to us what the naked eye can't see.
高科技，是吧？
Pretty far out, isn't it?
是啊，好神奇
Yeah, it's groovy.
德鲁，布拉德的摄像机准备好了吗？
Drew, you got the Bolex ready for Brad?
是的，一切就绪，先生
Yeah, already locked and loaded, sir.
怎么了？人有三急嘛
What? I had to go.
所有房间信号正常
All the rooms are coming in pretty good.
很好
Good.
瓶子里是什么？
What's in the bottle?
圣水
Holy water.
像这样的宗教信物…
Presence of religious icons...
…会让任何邪恶的东西起反应
...will get a reaction from anything unholy.
类似于激怒他们
Sort of pisses them off.
所以我满屋子都放了这些，看能不能占据点优势
So I set these throughout the house,see if I can stir things up a bit.
就像对着吸血鬼亮出十字架？  - 对，没错
Like holding a cross to a vampire?  - Yeah. Exactly.
除了我不相信有吸血鬼之外
Except I don't believe in vampires.
不是我
Wasn't me.
布拉德，拿上摄像机
Brad, get the camera.
好了
Okay.
现在是晚上9:18，我们准备进入地下室，刚才那里的门自己开了
All right, it's 9:18, we're headed down into the cellar where the door's just opened on its own.
罗琳跟布拉德警官跟我一起
I have Lorraine and Officer Brad Hamilton with me.
地下室的灯保持关闭
Let's keep the cellar light off.
如果想跟我们交流，就给我们点提示吧
Give us a sign that you wanna communicate with us.
亲爱的，你还好吗？
Hon, you all right?
这里肯定有什么东西
There's definitely something here.
关个门，移动点东西什么的  - 我的手很冷
All right, close the door. Move something.  - My hands are so cold.
来啊
Come on.
不
No.
它走了，它走了
It's gone. It's gone.
我什么都没录到
I got nothing.
好的
Okay.
就像我说的，并不是每次都能如愿以偿
Well, like I said, it doesn't always work when you want it to.
是啊，也许摄像机拍到了点什么
Yeah, maybe the camera picked something up.
小心！
Watch out!
作为无神论者…
For a guy who doesn't believe...
…门摔上的时候你们好像吓傻了嘛
...you looked a little freaked out when that door slammed shut.
肯定是风
It must have been a draft.
噢，滑稽
Oh, that's funny.
风从来不会让我出现那种表情
A draft never put that look on my face before.
我更相信那钟
I believe the clock.
3:08了
It's 3:08.
给我看看你的眼镜
Let me see your glasses.
给你的
For you.
待会儿我想带几个女孩子去吃冰激淋，觉得怎么样？
I think I might take some girls for ice cream later on. What do you say about that?
好的！  - 亲爱的，一起吗？
Yeah!  - Honey, you wanna come?
我累死了，我要睡一会儿，好困
I'm exhausted. I'm just gonna take a nap.The late nights are getting to me.
好主意，你休息一会儿吧
That's probably a good idea.Why don't you get some rest.
罗琳和我会照看这里  - 真的吗？
Lorraine and I'll watch over things for a bit.  - Really?
我要出发了，一小时后我有活
I'm gonna take off.I have a shift starting in an hour.
这个家很久都没有这样了
The house hasn't felt like this in a long time.
有你们在，孩子们有安全感多了
I think the kids feel a lot safer with you around.
我会习惯起来的  - 什么？我洗衣服？
I could get used to this.  - What, me doing laundry?
你真幽默
You're funny.
这地方…
No, this place.
漂亮，新鲜的乡村空气
Nice, fresh country air.
他们有个很幸福的家，是吧？
They have such a beautiful family,don't they?
是啊，那小家伙，艾普丽尔，有没有看到她给我拿煎饼？
Yeah, that little one, April,did you see her bring me pancakes?
是的
Yeah!
我们得帮他们
We've gotta help them.
我知道
I know.
从修好那辆车开始
I'll start with the Chevy.
卡洛琳！
Carolyn!
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
卡洛琳，开门
Carolyn, open the door.
卡洛琳，快开门！
Carolyn, open up!
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
我没事  - 你病了吗？
Oh, I'm fine.  - Are you sick?
我醒过来感觉有点想吐，仅此而已  - 我看到了…
I woke up feeling nauseous, that's all.  - I thought I saw...
我听到罗杰跟孩子们回来了
I hear Roger and the girls.
稍等
One minute.
姐妹们，想玩游戏吗？  - 无聊！
Guys, do you wanna play a game?  - Boring!
谢谢，爸爸
Thank you, Daddy.
我们进去吧
Let's go inside.
就知道是你
I thought that was you.
希望你不要介意
Hey, I hope you don't mind.
我在史密斯菲尔德的废车场低价买了个拆车件
I got a good deal on a rebuild at that wrecking yard in Smithfield.
不，你看起来很精通啊  - 是的，瞧我的
No, you look like you know what you're doing.  - Yeah, we'll see.
这地方不错，罗杰
Got a nice place here, Roger.
罗琳跟我一直想在乡下买套房子
Lorraine and I always wanted a spot in the country.
我把这里卖给你吧
I'll sell you this one.
把扳手递给我
Hey, hand me a wrench, would you?
嗨，你们能来这里，真是感激不尽
Hey, uh, it really means a lot to us to have you here.
我承认，之前我是有点不相信这些
I gotta admit, I was a little bit skeptical going in.
就想说一声谢谢，对于你们所做的一切
Just wanna say thank you, though,for coming out when you did.
我不能接受这份谢意，这都是罗琳的功劳
I can't take the credit.That's, uh... That's all Lorraine.
我并不想这么做  - 为什么？
I didn't want to.  - Oh. Why's that?
罗琳所看到的、感受到的、接触到的，可以帮助别人
Whatever Lorraine sees, feels, touches,it helps people.
但同时也会给她带来伤害
But it also takes a toll on her.
每次一点点
Little piece each time.
几个月前，我们正在处理一个案子
Couple months ago we were working on a case.
她看到了一些东西
She saw something.
造成了很大的伤害
It took a real big piece.
我们回家后…
When we got home...
…她进了房间，把自己锁在了里面…
...she went into our room,locked herself in...
…整整八天，不说，不吃，不出门
...didn't talk, didn't eat,didn't come out for eight days.
她看到了什么？
What'd she see?
出去！
Get out of here!
不知道
I don't know.
我也不会问
And I won't ask.
我要再去倒一杯，你要吗？
I need to reload. You want some?
不用，谢谢
I'm good, thanks.
好吧
All right.
看看她都让我干了些什么
Look what she made me do.
嗨
Hey.
艾德？
Ed?
看看她都让我干了些什么
Look what she made me do!
艾德！艾德！
Ed! Ed!
艾德！
Ed!
哥们儿，你还好吗？
Dude, you okay?
冷静点，布拉德，怎么了？
Hold up, Brad. What's going on?
我看到了一个穿着佣人服的女人
I saw someone. There was a woman dressed as a maid.
艾德？艾德，有情况
Ed? Ed, we're getting something.
是辛蒂，她在梦游  - 不，等等
It's just Cindy. She's sleepwalking.  - No, wait. We need this.
为什么要给辛蒂拍照？
Why do we need pictures of Cindy?
不是她激发的
She didn't trigger it.
不是她激发的？什么意思？  - 有人跟她在一起
What do you mean she didn't trigger it?  - Somebody's with her.
谁？
Who?
辛蒂！
Cindy!
过来这里，这里安全
Hey, over here. It's safe.
有人跟她在一起
There's someone else in there with her.
我听到了另一个声音，这里，听
I'm hearing another voice. Here, listen.
跟我来，这边走
Follow me. This way.
这就是我躲的地方
This is where I hide.
辛蒂？
Cindy?
她去哪里了，艾德？
Where'd she go, Ed?
窗子都锁上了
Windows are locked.
艾德，她去哪里了？
Ed, where'd she go?
布拉德，把紫外灯拿来
Brad, get the UV light.
什么？  - 问德鲁
The what?  - Just ask Drew.
德鲁，我要个紫外灯
Drew, I need a UV light.
给，就这个，快去，快去！
Here, that's it. Go, go, go, go!
关灯
Turn off the light.
让开
Get out of the way.
好的
Okay.
开灯！
Hit the lights!
找到她了
Found her.
过来吧
Here we go.
抱好了？  - 是的
All right. You got her?  - Yeah.
那就是罗利害怕的时候躲的地方
That's where Rory hides when he's afraid.
亲爱的？把艾普丽尔的音乐盒给我
Hon? Could I have April's music box, please?
辛蒂怎么样？  - 她什么都不记得
How's Cindy?  - She doesn't remember a thing.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
罗琳！
Lorraine!
不
No.
罗琳！
Lorraine!
是她让我这么做的
She made me do it.
艾德！
Ed!
拜托！罗琳！
Come on! Lorraine!
艾德！
Ed!
艾德，我知道她做了什么
Ed, I know what she did.
我扶你，我知道，没事了  - 我知道她做了什么
I got you. I know. It's okay.  - I know what she did.
我知道她做了什么，她附身在那妈妈身上杀了那孩子
I know what she did. She possessed the mother to kill the child.
她每晚都会去卡洛琳那里
She visits Carolyn every night.
所以才会有那些淤青！她在吸食她！
That's what the bruise marks are!She's feeding off of her!
呃…
Uh....
南希？
Nancy?
南希！
Nancy!
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
南希！
Nancy!
抓住她！
Grab her!
爸爸！救命！
Daddy! Help!
南希！
Nancy!
她还好吗？
Is she okay?
没事了，没事了
It's okay, I got you.
拍到了吗？
Did you get that?
是的
Yeah.
我去冲印胶片，然后拿给哥顿神父
I'll have the footage developed and get it over to Father Gordon.
他是我们教堂方面的联络人，我们会很快得到回应的
He's our liaison at the church.I imagine we'll get a pretty fast response.
听着，罗杰？  - 什么？
Listen, Roger?  - Yeah?
听着，我们接到驱魔人就会回来，但罗琳…
Listen, when we get the exorcist,I'll be back. But Lorraine--
是的，我明白  - 在这之前，德鲁会照看你们的
Yeah, I understand.  - Until then Drew's gonna keep an eye on you.
艾德，感谢你所做的一切  - 嗯
Hey, Ed, thank you for everything.  - Yeah.
妈咪？
Mommy?
就这些了
That's everything.
妈咪？
Mommy?
朱蒂？
Judy?
噢，上帝啊！
Oh, God!
朱蒂？
Judy?
罗琳！等等！
Lorraine! Wait!
罗琳，怎么了？
Lorraine. What?
妈妈，是我，朱蒂还好吗？
Mom, it's me. Is Judy okay?
什么？  - 可以去看一下吗？
What?  - Can you go check, please?
该死的，妈妈，去看一下就是了！
Damn it, Mom, just check, please!
可以告诉我到底怎么了吗？  - 是朱蒂
Are you gonna tell me what's going on?  - It's Judy.
什么？什么意思？
What? What do you mean?
什么意思？
What?
噢，谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
妈妈，对不起，我不是有意要吓你的，回头再跟你解释
Mom, I'm sorry, I didn't mean to scare you. I'll explain later, okay?
这他妈到底怎么回事？
What the hell happened?
我看到朱蒂在湖里
I had a vision of Judy in the water.
我知道这是某种警告
I know it was some kind of warning.
我知道的
I know it.
好了
Okay.
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
然后？  - 嗯，你们不是开玩笑
So?  - Yeah, well, you weren't kidding.
是的
No.
艾德，这事有点复杂，因为那些孩子们没有经过洗礼
Look, Ed, this is complicated because the kids aren't baptized.
是的，我理解  - 那家人也不是教会成员
No, I understand.  - And the family are not members of the church.
噢，拜托  - 还有…
Oh, come on.  - And....
许可令必须由梵蒂冈直接下发
The approval would have to come directly from the Vatican.
神父，我们从没见过这样的东西
Father, we've never seen nothing like this.
是的，我也没见过
Yeah, well, neither have l.
神父，他们没那么多时间了
Father, they don't have a lot of time.
好吧
All right.
我会亲自跟进这事的
I'll push it through myself.
谢谢，神父，谢谢  - 谢谢
Thank you, Father. Thank you.  - Thank you.
我们等你电话  - 好的
All right, we'll wait for your call.  - Yeah.
妈妈？爸爸？
Mommy? Daddy?
妈妈？
Mommy?
爸爸？
Daddy?
Dad?
外婆？
Nanna?
外婆！
Nanna!
外婆，救命！外婆，救命！
Nanna, help! Nanna, help!
朱蒂？
Judy?
外婆！
Nanna!
救命！
Help!
朱蒂！  - 外婆！
Judy!  - Nanna!
朱蒂，开门！  - 妈妈！
Judy, open the door!  - Mom!
艾德，有点不对劲  - 什么？
Ed, there's something wrong.  - What?
外婆！
Nanna!
朱蒂！  - 救命！
Judy!  - Help!
朱蒂！朱蒂，开门！  - 怎么了？
Judy! Judy, open this door!  - What is it?
她怎么了？朱蒂！  - 让开，让开，让开，让开
What's wrong with her? Judy!  - Hey, move. Move, move, move, move.
朱蒂，退后，宝贝，退后
Judy, get back, honey. Get back!
拜托！  - 快点
Come on!  - Hurry.
救命！救命！
Help! Help!
离门远一点，朱蒂！
Get away from the door, Judy!
噢，上帝！你没事吧？
Oh, God! Are you okay?
有个人在跟安娜贝尔一起摇椅子
There was someone rocking in the chair with Annabelle.
什么？
What?
没事了
It's okay.
她还在箱子里
She's still in the case.
没事了
It's okay.
没事了，没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
爸爸！爸爸！  - 爸爸！
Dad! Dad!  - Daddy!
爸爸！爸爸！妈妈带着克里斯蒂和艾普丽尔走了
Dad! Dad! Mom just left with Christine and April.
她进了车子然后开走了，我不知道发生了什么事
She went in the car and drove away.I don't know what happened.
她闻起来有股烂肉味道  - 她没说到底是怎么了
She smells like rotting meat.  - She didn't say what was going on.
她走了是什么意思？走去哪了？  - 就是走了！不知道去哪里了
What do you mean, she left? Left where?  - Gone! I don't know where she was going.
我们去哪，妈妈？
Where are we going, Mom?
喂？  - 我是罗杰
Hello?  - It's Roger.
有事发生在卡洛琳身上了
Something's going on with Carolyn.
安德莉亚在，她说卡洛琳带着克里斯蒂和艾普丽尔走了
Andrea was here,said Carolyn took off with Christine and April.
孩子们说她闻起来像块烂肉  - 附身于母亲…
The girls said she smelled like rotten meat.  - Possesses the mother...
…来杀掉孩子，她就是这么做的，她要把她们带去那房子
...to kill the child, that's what she does.She's taking them to the house.
罗杰，现在去房子里，我在那跟你碰头
Roger, get back to the house now.I'll meet you there.
锁上门，拉上窗帘，远离电话
Lock the door, close the blinds.Stay off the phone!
走
Go.
我跟你一起去  - 不行，你陪着朱蒂
I'm coming with you.  - Noway, you stay with Judy.
保护朱蒂的唯一办法就是终结这一切
Only way to protect Judy is if we stop this where it started.
否则她会再次缠上我们  - 这正是我要去做的
Otherwise, she'll latch onto us again.  - That's exactly why I am going.
你觉得我会让你一个人去吗？
You think I'm gonna let you walk into this alone?
我不能失去你
I can't lose you.
你不会的
You won't.
我们一起把这事终结吧
Let's finish this together.
锁上了  - 卡洛琳！
Agh! It's locked.  - Carolyn!
罗杰！
Roger!
让开！
Get out of the way!
罗杰！  - 艾德！
Roger!  - Ed!
卡洛琳！  - 艾德！
Carolyn!  - Ed!
卡洛琳！  - 我们在这里！
Carolyn!  - We're down here!
卡洛琳，不要！不，不！她抓着…！
Carolyn, don't!No, no! She's got...!
抓住她手！把剪刀夺下来！
Get her hand! Get the scissors!
我们得把她带到车里！  - 然后把她带去哪？
We gotta get her to the car!  - And bring her where?
把她带到神父那里驱魔
To take her to the priest for the exorcism.
艾普丽尔在哪？  - 艾普丽尔？
Where's April?  - April?
艾普丽尔！
April!
把克里斯蒂带上车，把艾普丽尔找出来！
Take Christine to the car and find April!
艾普丽尔！
April!
赶紧！
Come on!
她不让她离开这房子  - 什么意思？
She won't let her leave the house.  - What do you mean?
如果把她带出来，女巫会杀了她的
If we take her out, the witch will kill her.
罗杰！
Roger!
卡洛琳！
Carolyn!
快去！
Go!
卡洛琳！
Carolyn?
我把你放在这里，来
Okay, I'm gonna put you in here.Come on.
进去，呆里面  - 我不想一个人在这里
Get in. Stay in here.  - I don't wanna stay here by myself.
呆在这里，我很快回来
Stay in here no matter what.I'll be back.
我要去找艾普丽尔，知道吗？很快回来，我发誓
I have to find April, okay?I'll be back, I promise.
艾普丽尔？
April?
你没事吧？
You okay?
住手！
Stop!
布拉德！布拉德！
Brad! Brad!
找点什么东西把她绑起来
Let's get something to tie her up!
按住
Hold it.
我得打电话把哥顿神父叫过来
I gotta call Father Gordon.We gotta get him out here.
他离的太远了，她撑不了那么久，看看她
He's too far away.She won't make it. Look at her.
那你得离开了  - 你在说什么？
Then you need to leave.  - What are you talking about?
我得进行驱魔仪式
I have to do it. The exorcism.
什么？你不是说需要一个神父吗，你又不是神父
What? I thought you said we need a priest. You're not a priest.
你有更好的主意？  - 他可以的
Well, you got a better idea?  - He can do it.
你可以的  - 但你得离开这里
You can do it.  - But you gotta get out of here.
我不会离开你！  - 该死的，你不能在这里！
I'm not leaving you!  - Damn it, I'm not doing this with you in here!
上帝把我们撮合在一起是有原因的，就这样
God brought us together for a reason.This is it.
我去拿书
I'm gonna get the book.
艾普丽尔！
April!
“以吾圣父，圣子，圣灵之名”
"In the name of the Father,the Son, the Holy Spirit."
艾普丽尔！
April!
按住她！按住她！
Hold her still! Hold her still!
过来！按住她！
Come here! Hold her still!
艾普丽尔？
April?
艾普丽尔！
April!
艾普丽尔，你在下面吗？
April, you under there?
艾普丽尔！
April!
卡洛琳，卡洛琳，别放弃！别让她占有你！
Carolyn. Carolyn. Don't give in!Don't let her take you!
艾德！不能再继续了，你会杀了她的，住手！
Ed! You gotta stop,you're killing her. Stop!
不，不能停！
No, he can't!
罗杰，救我！
Roger, help me!
艾德！该死的，住手！
Ed! Goddamn it, stop it!
记住！我们是在为她的灵魂做斗争！
Understand this! We are now fighting for her soul!
“以耶稣基督、圣人、天使之名…
"In the name of Jesus Christ,the saints and all the angels...
…我命令你揭开你的真面目！”
...I command you to reveal yourself!"
罗杰，救我！
Roger, help me!
放她下来！
Put her down!
卡洛琳！
Carolyn!
艾德，小心！
Ed, look out!
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
按住她！别让她再上去！
Hold her still! Don't let her up!
她快不行了，罗杰！
We're losing her, Roger!
去你的！离我家人远点，听到没有？
Damn you! You leave my family alone,you hear me?
我不知道你是谁，但离我妻子远一点，该死的！
I don't know what you are, but you leave my wife alone, goddamn it!
放开她！听到没？放开她！
Let her go!Do you hear me? Let her go!
放开她，该死的！放开她！
Let her go, goddamn it! Let her go!
她已经死了
She's already gone.
现在你们都得死
And now you're all gonna die.
艾普丽尔！
April!
找到她了！她在下面！厨房下面！
I found her! She's under the house!Under the kitchen!
不要！不！
Don't! No!
抓住她！
Get her!
给  - 卡洛琳！
Here.  - Carolyn!
卡洛琳！  - 她在那洞里，就在那里
Carolyn!  - She's in that hole. Right there.
卡洛琳？上帝啊，不！
Carolyn? Oh, my God. No!
进不去，够不到
Can't go in. Can't reach.
不！卡洛琳，不要！
No! Carolyn, don't!
卡洛琳，不要！
Carolyn, no!
巴斯希巴！
Bathsheba!
吾借上帝之力，命汝重回地狱！
By the power of God,I condemn you back to hell!
这是你女儿！
This is your daughter!
你不能屈服
You can't give in!
罗杰，我们得让她自己反抗
Roger. We need to get her to fight from the inside.
别让她这么做，别让那东西这么做！
Don't let her do this.Don't let this thing do this.
你要反抗，我知道你比她更强
You gotta fight it.I know you're stronger than she is.
你要跟它抗争！  - 继续，罗杰！
You gotta fight it!  - Keep it going, Roger!
别离开我们，好吗？回来，卡洛琳！
You gotta stay with us, all right?Come on back, Carolyn!
对了，就这样！带她回来！
You're in, that's it! Get her back!
想一想你给我看的照片  - 不！
Remember what you showed me.  - No!
想一想你说的那永世难忘的一天
Remember that day that you said you would never forget.
你说他们就是你的一切
You said they meant the world to you.
这些你都不要了吗？
This is what you'll be leaving behind.
妈妈？
Mommy?
都结束了
It's over.
真对不起
I am so sorry.
爱死你了，爱死你了
I love you so much. I love you so much.
爱死你了
I love you so much.
我太高兴了
I'm so happy.
是风把你脸弄成这样的吗？
A draft do that to your face?
我宁愿每天都面对持枪歹徒
I'd take a guy with a gun any day.
你做的很好
You did good.
不，你才是
No, you did.
我打个电话给哥顿神父，告诉他这一切
I'll call Father Gordon and let him know what happened.
听起来不错
Sounds good.
梵蒂冈批准了驱魔仪式
The Vatican approved the exorcism.
来的真是时候
Heh. Nice timing.
还有如果可以的话，他明天想见见我们
And if we can, then he'd like to meet with us tomorrow.
长岛有一个案子，他想跟我们讨论一下
There's a case in Long Island he'd like to discuss.
是吗？
Really?
“邪恶力量非常强大，至今一直存在着。这故事是真实的，恶魔和上帝确实存在。
对我们凡人而言，我们的命运取决于选择站在哪一边。”
- 艾德·沃伦
*佩伦一家*
*沃伦一家*